Lucky Luke is a comedy, western film directed by Terence Hill.
Lucky Luke becomes the Sheriff of Daisy Town and runs out all the criminals.
Then the Dalton brothers arrive and try to get the Indians to
break the peace treaty and attack the town.
Lucky Luke, played by Terence Hill.
Lotta Legs, played by Nancy Morgan.
Jolly Jumper, played by Roger Miller.
Joe Dalton, played by Ron Carey.
William Dalton, played by Dominic Barto.
Jack Dalton, played by Bo Greigh.
Lucky Luke is a 1991 Italian-American Western comedy film directed by and starring
Terence Hill and based on the Belgian comic book of the same name.
It is also the pilot episode of the Lucky Luke television series.
It was shot in Bonanza Creek Ranch and Santa Fe (New Mexico), Zia Pueblo, Valles Caldera National
Preserve, White Sands National Monument and La Junta (Colorado), and Tucson, Arizona.
The film explores themes of saloon, brother, horse, arrest, spaghetti western.
The tone is lighthearted.